[Music]
[音乐]
okay so welcome to the talk today on
好吧，欢迎今天的演讲
jane at five my name is Sam Brennan I'm
我五岁的简是我的名字是山姆·布伦南
a principal self engineer at pivotal
关键的首席自我工程师
since a few months so to speak
几个月以来
I've been a Java developer for over 20
我已经有20多个Java开发人员
years so quite a long time and I've been
好多年了，我一直
a committer for the Spring Framework
Spring框架的提交者
since 2007 where I originally um rewrote
自从2007年我最初重写
to the testing framework based on
到基于的测试框架
annotations with Jane Doe for testing D
Jane Doe批注以测试D
etc and I maintained that still today
等，我坚持到今天
and I've been a core committer for Jane
我一直是Jane的核心提交者
at five since October of 2015 so this
自2015年10月起在5点
combination is why I'm here talking to
组合就是为什么我在这里聊天
you today so we want to talk about today
今天是你，我们今天要谈
is what do you see in five in general
您在五个总体上看到什么
what is Jane and Jupiter specifically
简和木星到底是什么
I'll give you a few tips on migrating
我会给你一些迁移的技巧
from Jane at Ford if you choose to do
来自福特的简（如果您愿意的话）
that talk about some of the newer
谈论一些较新的
features since the original five will
自最初的五个功能以来
release a bit about the roadmap but we
发布有关路线图的一些信息，但我们
have planned and then a bit about using
已经计划，然后再使用
Gina Jupiter with spring and spring boot
吉娜·朱庇特（Gina Jupiter）
so before you're going like to see a
所以在你想看到一个
show of hands how many people write
举手示意有多少人写
tests hopefully one yes unit tests
希望测试一个是的单元测试
integration tests or people into in
集成测试或人员参与
tests if you were in fewer okay terms of
测试您是否在更少的条件下
frameworks how about a framework called
框架如何称为
Janet who uses that you watch everyone
珍妮特，谁看着你
anyone still on Jane at three no hands
三手无动的人仍然在简上
alright that's good who's on Jana for
好的，这是谁在Jana上
yeah latest in greatest for 12 most few
是的，最新的最多，只有12个
people okay right so the last release of
人们还好吧，所以最新发布的
Jana 4 is probably coming out in the
Jana 4可能会在
next month or so and that'll be Jane did
下个月左右，那将是简做的
413 it's into an already on Jane at five
413五点钟就已经进入简
change you've gone three or four people
改变你已经走了三四个人
anyone use anything different like Tess
任何人使用像苔丝一样的东西
in G one guy okay anyone use some like
在G中，一个人好，有人用
Spock yeah anything else like Kotlin
Spock是的，像Kotlin一样
tests and stuff like that pointed to
测试和诸如此类的内容
people okay
人们还好
so fewer and fewer so what is jr. five
越来越少，那么什么是小。五
well here we have the big picture so we
好在这里，我们有大局，所以我们
see at the bottom that we have this new
在底部看到我们有这个新
platform that's a new idea that's what
平台，这是一个新主意
the IDS and build tools we integrate
我们集成的IDS和构建工具
with you could use it on your own as
与您可以单独使用它
well if you want to but wouldn't be very
好吧，如果你想但不会很
likely instead you're plugging to use
相反，您可能正在使用
what we call a test engine in there
我们所谓的测试引擎
different ones we have one for a week
不同的，我们一个星期
all vintage instead of legacies
全年份而不是传统
supporting old cell tests with Jane at
支持简与旧的细胞测试
four and Gina three and we have the new
四和吉娜三，我们有新
stuff which is Jane a Jupiter and you
是简·木星和你的东西
could be using some other third-party
可能正在使用其他一些第三方
implementation or you could write your
实现或您可以编写您的
own so with Jane of five I kind of like
拥有五个珍妮，我有点喜欢
to use a joke based on the matrix there
根据那里的矩阵来开玩笑
is no spoon
不是汤匙
there is no Jane of five you can't just
没有五个珍妮，你不能只是
upgrade your your um your maven palms
升级您的乌鸦手掌
and Gradle didn't say a unit conversion
Gradle没有说单位换算
style five that doesn't work so actually
样式五实际上不起作用
with Jane of five we rewrote everything
与五岁的简一起重写了所有内容
and we now have kind of three main
现在我们有三种主要
categories of things we have a platform
我们拥有平台的事物类别
and we have Jupiter and we have
我们有木星，我们有
advantage so what is the platform this
优势，这是什么平台
is a foundation for launching testing
是启动测试的基础
frameworks on the JVM kind of a new idea
JVM上的框架有点新想法
we have a launcher API in there we have
我们有一个启动器API
test engine API that you can implement
您可以实现的测试引擎API
and we have a console launcher which is
我们有一个控制台启动器
a way to run this from the console we
从控制台运行此方法的方式
also have a standalone console launch
也有独立的控制台启动
your jar that you can download if you
您可以下载的jar，如果您
want so Jupiter that's actually the new
想要这样的木星实际上是新的
programming model and extension about
编程模型及其扩展
for Jane of five so its own size
五人的简
or when you read a blog I'm writing a
或者当您阅读博客时，我正在写
junior five test this is probably what
大三测试这可能是什么
they mean that they're using Jane at
他们的意思是他们在使用Jane
Jupiter and running on the platform and
木星并在平台上运行和
vintage that's an test engine
作为测试引擎的年份
implementation that allows you to use
允许您使用的实现
Jaina 3 and Jane you four based tests or
Jaina 3和Jane You四个基础测试或
other things like older versions of
其他诸如旧版本的
Spock other based on Gina 4 as well it's
Spock other也基于Gina 4
one thing I'd like to point out is that
我想指出的一件事是
this first block here is actually
这第一个街区实际上是
revolutionary that didn't exist before
以前不存在的革命者
people did write runners for Jane 4 but
人们确实为简4写过跑步者，但是
they were kind of forced to go with the
他们被迫与
Java model and the new platform is very
Java模型和新平台非常
generic and in many ways it supports
通用的，并且在许多方面都支持
files and directories and things like
文件和目录之类的东西
that in addition to Java classes and end
除了Java类和结束
methods so on the next part is
方法，所以下一部分是
evolutionary right that's where you want
进化权就是您想要的
to do things better or differently than
做事比做的更好或不同
things were done in Jane and forth and
事情在简中来回完成，
the last parts necessary because we want
最后的必要部分，因为我们想要
everyone's going to keep running their
每个人都将继续运行
Janie 3 tests and Jane for tests and
Janie 3测试，Jane测试和
Spock tests at the same time or
同时进行Spock测试或
simultaneously while running Jani G
在运行Jani G的同时
protests so in a nutshell chain of five
简而言之，抗议者只有五个人
is a complete rewrite of Jane it from
是对Jane的完整改写，来自
the ground up improving on what gene
不断完善什么基因
already had to offer but with the
已经不得不提供但与
extensibility and in mind and it's
可扩展性和思想，这是
modular extensible and modern rights
模块化可扩展的现代权利
based on Java 8
基于Java 8
another key thing that we had in mind or
我们想到的另一件事
kept in mind was wanted to be both
牢记要成为
forward and backward compatible at the
向前和向后兼容
same time so basically the platform
同时基本上是平台
supports jayna 3 8 and 4 with the
支持jayna 3 8和4
vintage engine and Jane and Jupiter with
老式引擎和简和木星与
the jupiter engine plus support for any
木星引擎以及任何支持
other test engines that someone has
某人拥有的其他测试引擎
written or that you may write on your
或您可以在自己的书上写
own and in fact people have already
自己的，实际上人们已经
written some test engines if you'd like
如果愿意的话，写一些测试引擎
to check out see what see what there is
看看看看有什么
just go to the wiki page for jane at 5
只需在5的wiki页面上找到简（Jane）
and go to the third party centers page
并转到第三方中心页面
and you see a list there i'm not only
你在那里看到清单，我不仅
test engines but also of about 20 or 30
测试引擎，但也有大约20或30
different extensions for G and Jupiter
G和木星的不同扩展
so things like spring and mojito and
像春天和莫吉托之类的东西
other stuff like that terms of Java
其他类似Java的术语
versions this is a bit of poetry I
版本，这是诗歌我
posted a while back on the Twitter world
在Twitter上发布了一段时间
so works great on J decade so that's the
因此在J十年中表现出色，因此
baseline for um jeito 5 works fine jdk 9
um jeito 5的基准工作正常jdk 9
with all i said at my automatic module
我在自动模块上说的所有
names in the jars and we're adding or
罐子里的名字，我们要添加或
shifting in 5/5 adding more support for
移入5/5，增加了对
real module info if we can get that
真实的模块信息，如果我们能得到的话
working we also support module path
工作，我们也支持模块路径
scanning in addition to classified
扫描除分类
scanning everything works again on jdk
扫描一切再次在jdk上工作
10 and 11
10和11
yes when I posted but now we're building
是的，当我发布但现在我们正在构建
against and testing against JDK 11 and
针对JDK 11进行测试
12 and we're trying with 13 but we have
12，我们正在尝试13，但我们有
some some issues not in our code but and
一些不是我们代码中的问题，而是
third parties and builds and stuff like
第三方和构建之类的东西
that so in terms of ideas and unbuilt
这样的想法和未建
support that's important to you because
支持对您很重要，因为
you actually want to be able to use this
您实际上希望能够使用此
stuff and good news all the major ideas
东西和好消息是所有主要思想
and build tools support it so tell
和构建工具支持它，所以告诉
Jason's idea 2016 to eclipse since
杰森（Jason）的想法2016年以来黯然失色
oxygen for seven one NetBeans more
多给七个NetBeans供氧
recently since Apache to NetBeans 10
从Apache到NetBeans 10以来的最新情况
dotto Gradle so we originally wrote our
dotto Gradle，所以我们最初写了我们的
own plugin I'm a grade alarm rode added
自己的插件，我是年级警报骑手
full first-class support in Gradle 4.6
在Gradle 4.6中提供全面的一流支持
may even came on a bit later
也许以后再来
surefire 2.22 and they've improved it
surefire 2.22，他们已经对其进行了改进
recently allowing Springview to to adopt
最近允许Springview采纳
Jane of five in the past couple of days
过去几天里的五个珍妮
so aunt um actually uh beat the maven
所以嗯嗯姨
team surprisingly and they have support
团队出奇的是，他们有支持
since aunt one 10.3
自10.3阿姨以来
so I'm not gonna show any examples how
所以我不会显示任何例子
to set this stuff up if you want to see
如果您想看到这些东西
that check out the user guide from jana
查阅jana的用户指南
5 as well as some of the sample
5以及一些样本
applications that we link to terms up on
我们链接到条款的应用程序
releases so 5.0 is released back in
发行，所以5.0重新发行了
September of 2017 since then we've had
从那时起2017年9月
five dot one two three and four releases
五点一二三和四发行
the most recent being fired at 4.2 so
最近被开除了4.2
that's what you should be using and
那就是你应该使用的
we're working on 5.5 as we speak so what
我们在讲话时正在研究5.5，所以
is Jane at Jupiter what is Jupiter
是木星的简什么是木星
that's not a trick question it's a
这不是一个技巧性的问题，而是
planet
行星
yes which planets the fifth planets yes
是的，哪颗行星是第五颗行星，是的
so Jane at five we didn't want to name
所以我们五岁的简不想
it Jane yet vibe because there might be
它简而充满活力，因为可能
a version six of it and we thought it
版本六，我们认为
would be grab their silly to have Jane
傻傻地拥有简
two five version six so we came up with
二五版本六，所以我们想出了
kind of a codename and Jupiter starts
一种代号，木星开始
with J you like Junior J unit and it's
和J一起，你喜欢Junior J单位，
also v so we thought that's a good name
也v，所以我们认为这是个好名字
in case you're wondering where the name
万一你想知道名字在哪里
came from so in a nutshell Jana Jupiter
简而言之来自Jana Jupiter
is a sub for the new program model and
是新程序模型的子项，并且
extension model in Jane of five the
简的五个扩展模型
program model that's how you write your
程序模型就是您编写代码的方式
tests the annotations you use the
测试您使用的注释
assertions use and assumptions and the
断言的使用和假设以及
types of tests or the style of tests
测试类型或测试样式
that you can write the extension model
您可以编写扩展模型
that's basically how you and third
那基本上就是你和第三个人
parties can extend the framework itself
各方可以扩展框架本身
so things like spring and maketo
所以像spring和maketo之类的东西
selenium etc so in Jane you fire J and
硒等，因此在Jane中，您解雇了J和
Jupiter we do have a more powerful
木星我们确实有更强大的
programming model basically ask yourself
编程模型基本上要问自己
what can you do a change Jupiter you
你能做什么改变木星你
couldn't do with Jane at for quite a bit
简与简无法相处
some things are simpler like visibility
有些事情更简单，例如能见度
we don't require things to be public
我们不要求公开事物
anymore they just some can't be private
他们只是一些不能私下
but you can choose package protected and
但您可以选择受保护的软件包
type less put your test classes and
少输入您的测试类，
method names and stuff like that we also
方法名称和类似的东西
support for custom display names so
支持自定义显示名称，因此
instead of the limitation based on the
而不是基于
technical names in Java you can use that
您可以使用Java中的技术名称
it's late name annotation and have
这是最新的名称注释，并具有
spaces special characters and even emoji
空格特殊字符甚至表情符号
and your display names if you want it's
和您的显示名称（如果需要）
inspired that for we have a new display
启发了这一点，因为我们有了新的展示
name generator' with some built-in
内置一些名称生成器
out-of-the-box support there and you can
开箱即用的支持，您可以
also write your own tagging you might
还可以编写自己的标签
know that idea from groups from testing
从测试小组中知道这个想法
Z or categories from J at four so in
Z或来自J的类别在4点如此
Dana Jupiter we have hat tag and that
Dana Jupiter，我们有帽子标签，那个
replaces the experimental category
取代实验类别
support that was there and change
在那里的支持和改变
or in addition we have a tag especially
或者除此之外，我们还有一个标签
language so you can say like this thing
语言，所以你可以说这样的事情
of this thing or this thing and not this
这个东西或这个东西而不是这个
thing and you can build up a tag
东西，你可以建立一个标签
expression to select which tests to run
选择要运行的测试的表达式
so here's an example um calculator tests
所以这是一个示例um计算器测试
nothing too crazy here but one things
这里没有什么太疯狂的，只有一件事
you notice right off the bat is that
您马上注意到，
there's no public key word here for the
这里没有公共关键字
class or for the method and in addition
类或方法以及其他
we see this a display name annotation
我们看到这个显示名称注释
that's optional you don't have to do
这是可选的，您不必做
what you can so you can give meaningful
你可以做什么，所以你可以给予有意义的
names and you can use as I mentioned
名称，您可以使用我提到的
before emoji and stuff like that another
在表情符号和类似的东西之前
thing to notice here is that we have
这里要注意的是，我们有
almost are equals so the method looks
几乎等于，所以该方法看起来
about the same but we have the the
差不多，但是我们有
message the failure message in case it
通知失败消息以防万一
fails at the end that comes now at the
最终在现在失败了
end instead of first so if you're
结束而不是首先，所以如果你是
migrating you would no doubt some tools
迁移您无疑会使用一些工具
will help you do it another thing to
会帮你做另一件事
note here is that this is a as a lambda
注意这里是作为lambda
expression here so basically we lazily
在这里表达，所以基本上我们懒惰
build up the exception messages if
建立异常消息，如果
you're doing some high string
你在做一些高弦
concatenation or something that took a
串联或其他花费
long time right because you want your
很长一段时间吧，因为你想要你的
test suite to run as fast as possible
测试套件以尽可能快的速度运行
here we see another example again using
在这里，我们再次使用另一个示例
some special characters in this play
该剧中一些特殊人物
name but something different here this
名字，但是这里有些不同
is also coming in June of 413 but we
也将在413年6月降临，但我们
write up rather since the start and Jana
从一开始就写
Jupiter so it start throws this is how
木星，所以它开始抛出这是如何
we do em exception handling testing for
我们对它们进行异常处理测试
exceptions in the modern world so to
现代世界的例外
speak so we say well we expect it to
说话，所以我们说得很好，我们希望它能够
thrown and then we have a lambda
抛出，然后我们有一个lambda
expression or method reference that's
表达式或方法引用
supposed to throw that kind of exception
应该抛出这种异常
and if it doesn't then you get a failure
如果没有，那么你会失败
in otherwise you get a reference to the
否则您将获得对
exception and then you can check other
异常，然后您可以检查其他
things about it like the COS of the
关于它的事情像
message etc similarly for timeouts we
消息等类似的超时
also have a similar way to do that with
也有类似的方法
lambda expressions so we have two
lambda表达式，所以我们有两个
methods in the assertions class we have
断言类中的方法
assert timeout and timeout preemptively
断言超时和超时
so this first one is a certain time off
所以这第一个要休息
what that's gonna do is gonna basically
那将要做的基本上是
wait on the code to complete so the code
等待代码完成，以便代码
never completes it could run forever but
永远不会完成，它可以永远运行，但是
if it doesn't then basically we just
如果没有，那么基本上我们只是
check how long it took afterwards and
检查之后花了多长时间，
and and fail the test if it takes you
并通过测试，如果需要你
long and the other option is to say
长，另一种选择是说
assert timeout preemptively and in that
抢先断言超时，并且
case what's gonna happen is the code is
情况将要发生的是代码是
gonna run in a separate thread and that
要在一个单独的线程中运行
means it'll be killed off if it takes
意味着如果需要它将会被杀死
you long so you might want you might
你很久，所以你可能想要你可能
prefer that but with the ladder you have
更喜欢那个，但是有了梯子
to keep in mind if you're using
要记住，如果您正在使用
frameworks or any kind of tooling that
框架或任何种类的工具
some has something bound to the thread
一些与线程绑定
with like a thread local for example in
与像本地线程一样
spring you have transaction management
春天你有交易管理
it's tied to the current thread for your
它绑定到您的当前线程
tests if you have a transaction on your
测试您是否有交易
tests and that would mean that your the
测试，这意味着您的
code running here
在这里运行的代码
not running this ring managed
没有运行此环管理
transaction so that's something you have
交易，这就是你所拥有的
to keep in mind with that so basic demo
牢记这一基本演示
just to show it all working you should
只是为了展示一切，你应该
have that calculated test in place we
有适当的计算测试
run it shouldn't be all too exciting but
运行它不应该太令人兴奋，但是
we would see for example an eclipse that
例如，我们会看到
that ran with they call it Jaina 5 they
与他们一起跑的叫吉安娜5他们
mean it ran on the platform and then it
表示它在平台上运行，然后
looks pretty much so much what we've
看起来非常我们所拥有的
seen before but we see we have some
见过但我们看到我们有一些
synthesis here right so this was must
合成在这里，所以这是必须的
have been a custom display name or you
一直是自定义显示名称，或者您
can double click on that and it goes
可以双击它去
straight to the method so in the
直接使用方法
background is tied technically to the
背景在技术上与
methods and the classes but the display
方法和类，但显示
name is just something human readable
名字只是人类可读的东西
which you can use if you want and here
如果需要，可以在这里使用
we have the example if it starts out
我们有一个例子，如果它开始
primitively
本来
and the throwing the exception here so
并在这里抛出异常
example if we made this take longer I
例如，如果我们花了更长的时间
guess is here if it takes we say
猜猜这里是否需要我们说
something like 45 it would take too long
大约45会花太长时间
if we run the test again then we should
如果我们再次运行测试，那么我们应该
hopefully see a failure but with
希望看到失败，但是
preemptively it actually stopped
先发制人地实际上停止了
therefore they're a thousand
因此他们是一千
milliseconds right so we don't know how
毫秒，所以我们不知道如何
long would it took but we see that it
需要多长时间，但我们看到了
failed so we have options like that and
失败了，所以我们有这样的选择，
again the class doesn't have to be
再次，不必上课
public and the methods don't have to be
公开的方法不必
public one thing to note is that the
公众要注意的一件事是
test annotation is in a different
测试注释位于不同的位置
package so it might catch you off-guard
包装，以防您措手不及
okay so we have even more power in
好吧，所以我们有更多的力量
expressive this meta annotation support
表达此元注释支持
so a meta annotation is an annotation on
因此，元注解是对
top of another annotation it's kind of
在另一个注释的顶部
like inheritance or annotations in Java
像Java中的继承或注释
and what it means when we say that we
当我们说我们
support that is you can use any of the
支持，您可以使用任何
annotations in JUnit as meta annotation
JUnit中的注释作为元注释
so you can combine annotations much like
因此您可以像
you may have already seen with spring
你可能已经在春天见过
over the years so you can create your
这些年来，您可以创建自己的
own custom composed annotations you can
您可以自定义组成的注释
also combine them with spring so spring
也把它们和春天结合起来
supports it and junior supports it that
支持它，而初级支持它
means you can use this feature together
表示您可以一起使用此功能
we also have something called
我们也有一个叫做
conditional test execution so Jana
有条件的测试执行，所以贾娜
forges hat Haddad ignore write and
伪造帽子哈达德忽略写和
you'll see we have more more than that
你会看到我们还有更多
another thing we have is dependency
我们有另一件事是依赖
injection for constructors and methods
构造函数和方法的注入
of your test methods and also your
您的测试方法以及您的
lifecycle methods like your before and
像您之前和之后那样的生命周期方法
after methods and stuff like that
之后的方法和类似的东西
land expressions and meth references can
陆地表达式和方法参考可以
be used in various places as we've just
正如我们刚刚在各个地方使用
seen for some of the assertions also for
看到一些断言也为
assumptions and
假设和
dynamic tests another thing that comes
动态测试另一件事
along with Java eight did a lot of
与Java 8一起做了很多
people home wouldn't actually think
人们回家实际上不会
about maybe on their own we have this
大概是我们自己有
new thing unless a new wooden job here
新事物，除非这里有新的木工
we have all methods and interfaces and
我们拥有所有方法和接口，
when you have that you basically can
当你拥有的时候，你基本上可以
have multiple inheritance and I like to
有多重继承，我喜欢
call it testing trait so you can have
称它为测试特质，所以你可以
test classes that implement certain
实现某些功能的测试类
interfaces and those interfaces can
接口，这些接口可以
already have tenth methods defined or
已经定义了第十种方法或
either configuration setup and teardown
配置设置和拆卸
to find so you can basically implement
找到，以便您基本上可以实施
some testing traits and then override
一些测试特征，然后覆盖
some abstract methods and have kind of a
一些抽象的方法，并有一种
TCK or testing kits like that
TCK或类似的测试套件
another feature um there was some
另一个功能，嗯，有一些
support for this was changing for some
对此的支持正在改变
external runners third parties we have
我们拥有的外部跑步者第三方
support order called nested test classes
支持顺序称为嵌套测试类
so you can have test classes inside test
这样您就可以在测试中包含测试类
classes and it adds a nice way or
类，它添加了一个不错的方法，或者
introduces a nice way to group your test
介绍了一种对测试进行分组的好方法
classes hierarchically and also in terms
类别和术语
of saving shared estate and setup we
保存共享财产和设置我们
also have repeated tests parametrize
也有反复测试参数
tests and test factories for dynamic
测试和测试工厂的动态
tests so we'll take a look at those
测试，所以我们来看看那些
another thing a lot of people don't know
很多人不知道的另一件事
about Janet for is that Janet has always
关于珍妮特的原因是珍妮特一直
instantiate adhere class a new so new
实例化坚持新的课程
instance every time it ran a test method
实例每次运行测试方法
and testing frameworks like session G
和测试框架（如会话G）
did the opposite of that they cashed it
他们兑现了相反的结果
and so what we have in Jana jupiter's we
所以我们在贾纳木星中所拥有的
give you an option so by default it
给你一个选择，所以默认情况下
works the whole way using a new instance
使用新实例可以全面工作
every time you can say test instance per
每次您可以说每个测试实例
class and get and they get one cashed
上课并获得，他们获得了一笔现金
and that has some benefits as well
这也有一些好处
tagging and custom annotations so for
标记和自定义注释
tagging all you have to do is um write
标记所有您要做的就是写
that tag on an interface class or method
接口类或方法上的那个标签
and give it a string like this tag fast
并快速给它一个像这个标签的字符串
and it's my fast test but maybe don't
这是我的快速测试，但也许不
want to repeat that all over the place
想在整个地方重复
maybe you want to change the name at
也许您想在以下位置更改名称
some point so you can actually come up
有一点，所以你实际上可以
with custom tags you can use the tag
使用自定义标签，您可以使用标签
annotation from Janet as a meditation on
来自Janet的注解，作为对
your own annotation so here we're
您自己的注释，所以在这里
writing our own fast annotation we've
编写我们自己的快速注释
annotated that with that tag fast then
然后用那个标签快速注释
we can just say add fast and that test
我们可以说快速添加和测试
throughout our code base and we kind of
在我们的代码库中，我们有点
reuse that but we can even go one step
重用它，但我们甚至可以迈出一步
further submit and you can combine
进一步提交，您可以合并
different annotations we call those
我们称这些为不同的注释
compose annotations and here we see an
撰写注释，在这里我们看到一个
example with two different annotations
具有两个不同注释的示例
from from Dana Jupiter we have the ID
来自Dana Jupiter，我们有ID
tag annotation and we have that test
标签注释，我们进行了测试
annotation and now we're saying add five
注释，现在我们说添加五个
test right so you can use that across
测试正确，这样您就可以跨
our codebase another thing you might
我们的代码库您可能会做的另一件事
have is a CI test or integration test or
有CI测试或集成测试，或
a slow test or something like that so
缓慢的测试或类似的东西
there are ways to categorize your tests
有一些方法可以对您的测试进行分类
and have a standard way to do it and
并有一个标准的方法来做到
then a standard set of tags that you use
然后是您使用的一组标准标签
for your build and locally so next up
用于您的构建和本地，因此下一步
more advanced repeated tests if you have
如果您有更高级的重复测试
something maybe a little flaking you
有些东西可能会剥落您
want to make sure or make sure something
想要确定或确定某事
is idempotent run a couple times in a
是幂等的
row you could say at repeated tests and
您可以在重复测试中说
then give it a number you can optionally
然后给它一个号码，您可以选择
accept a reference to the repetition
接受重复
info that allows you to find the total
可以让您找到总数的信息
number of petitions or the current
请愿数或当前
repetition if that helps you but that's
重复是否对您有帮助，但这是
not required and they really no example
不需要，他们真的没有例子
you can also override the name of the
您还可以覆盖
test here's a translation into two
测试这是一分为二的翻译
German so we do get access to the
德语，因此我们可以访问
current repetition and the total
当前重复次数和总数
repetitions and we'll see that actually
重复，我们会看到实际上
running in the IDE next up pretty much
接下来在IDE中运行
tests on that existed already with Jane
简的测试已经存在
and for it's a bit different in Jana
因为在Jana中有些不同
Jupiter and I'm actually a lot more
木星和我实际上更多
powerful in many ways so basically you
在很多方面都很强大，所以基本上您
annotate to method with @param tries
用@param尝试注释方法
test instead of test and you specify the
测试而不是测试，您可以指定
source of the arguments where they come
争论的来历
from you can optionally override the
从您可以选择覆盖
display name so much of what we just saw
显示名称，就像我们刚才看到的一样
with the repeated tests so for the
经过反复测试，因此
sources on there multiple or down the
多个或下方的来源
box at value source is the simplest it
价值来源的方框最简单
allows you to specify on your basic
允许您指定基本
primitive types strings or classes and
基本类型字符串或类，以及
in the next version also boolean's as
在下一版本中，布尔值也为
well there's also support for null
嗯，也支持null
sources and empty sources for things
事物的来源和空来源
like lists or strings and arrays and so
如列表或字符串和数组等等
like that enum source allows you to UM
像这样的枚举源可以让您使用UM
get access to the enum constants from
从以下位置获取枚举常量
particular enum method source is
特定的枚举方法的来源是
basically a factory method where you
基本上是工厂方法
write the code on your own to generate
自行编写代码以生成
to the list or the set of arguments you
到列表或参数集
want to use and then we have another
想使用，然后我们有另一个
thing called I'm CSV source so using the
所谓的我是CSV来源，因此使用
comma separated value lists that style
逗号分隔值列表，该样式
you can do it in line with CSV source in
您可以根据CSV源中的
the code or you can actually reference a
该代码，或者您可以实际引用
file in your class path with the add CSV
类文件中添加CSV文件
file source
档案来源
annotation and if those things don't
注释，如果那些东西没有
work out where you can write your own by
找出可以写自己的地方
implementing your own argument provider
实现自己的参数提供程序
and configuring that we're declaring
并配置我们要声明的
that without arguments source in all
全部没有参数来源
terms of conversion in aggregation for
汇总中的转化条件
the arguments we have support for that
我们支持的论点
first up we have implicit can
首先我们有隐式罐头
version four very common things so like
版本四非常普通的事情，像
primitive types in their wrappers so
包装器中的原始类型，因此
coming from a string where it's a string
来自一个字符串，它是一个字符串
and it's the you know 42 then you can
那是你知道的42那么你可以
get converted to an int or a long and
转换为int或long并
stuff like that we also support for
类似的东西，我们也支持
going from you know constant names into
从您知道的常量名称变为
you know constants things like files
你知道常量之类的文件
URLs currency locale things like that as
URL货币语言环境之类的东西
well
好
also um time think switch out of time so
也是时间，认为切换时间，所以
local date time you might want to have
您可能想要的本地日期时间
that converted and used as a parameter
转换并用作参数的
for your method and then more recently
为您的方法，然后是最近
we have support for um factory
我们对um工厂有支持
constructors and Static factory methods
构造函数和静态工厂方法
in particular classes as a fallback
在特定类中作为后备
mechanism and you can check out the
机制，您可以查看
documentation for that now in terms of
现在的文档
explicit conversion if that's that
明确的转换
doesn't work you can always provide your
不起作用，您可以随时提供您的
own conversion you can do that by
自己的转换，您可以通过
implementing your own arguments
实现自己的论点
converter and then just configuring that
转换器，然后进行配置
with at convert with we also have
与at转换一起，我们也有
support for patterns with the Java time
支持Java时间模式
conversion so you can specify particular
转换，因此您可以指定特定
pattern for that for the date format
日期格式的模式
with a time format coming from Europe
来自欧洲的时间格式
from your source from a CSV file for
从您的CSV文件中获取
example and more recently we have
例子，最近我们有
support for what's known as argument
支持所谓的论点
aggregation so basically if you're
因此，基本上，如果您
reading it from a CSV file and maybe on
从CSV文件读取它，也许在
the line represents a particular order
这条线代表一个特定的订单
or a person write all the fields you
或一个人写下您所有的字段
might want to have just the person
可能只想拥有那个人
object inject it into your test method
对象将其注入您的测试方法
and you can write I use aggregation for
你可以写我使用聚合
that the way you would do that is you
那你做的方式就是你
could use the arguments API or implement
可以使用参数API或实现
an argument aggregator and that would
一个参数聚合器
then take all the input for a given set
然后取给定集合的所有输入
of values and then create one object so
值，然后创建一个对象
that's somewhat similar to the raw
这有点像原始的
mapper from spring JDBC support you know
您知道Spring JDBC支持中的mapper
that here we have a concrete example we
在这里，我们有一个具体的例子
have a parametrized test when you have
当你有一个参数化的测试
said we want this to be a parametrized
说我们希望这是一个参数化
test and for the source we're picking
测试，我们选择来源
add value source in this case you're
在这种情况下，您可以增加价值来源
picking strings so just a set of strings
挑选字符串，所以只是一组字符串
here and this method will then be
在这里，这种方法将是
invoked five times once for each of
每次被调用五次
these strings and the string just gets
这些字符串，字符串就可以了
passed in as a candidate and we can
通过作为候选人，我们可以
check for example our is palindrome
例如检查我们的回文
method is working properly
方法工作正常
another option i mention is to have your
我提到的另一种选择是让你的
own factory method instead of using the
自己的工厂方法，而不是使用
value source you can say add method
您可以说增值方法的价值来源
source originally you had to specify the
原始来源，您必须指定
name but in a more recent release we
名称，但在最新版本中，我们
also support the convention if the test
如果测试也支持约定
method name is the same as the factory
方法名称与工厂相同
method
方法
have to clear our specify it so this
必须清除我们指定的内容，这样
would actually invoke this method here
实际上会在这里调用此方法
and whatever stream it returns here
以及它返回的任何流
those would then be the inputs for this
这些将是为此的输入
for this method in just a wee
这种方法只需要一点点
parametrized dynamic test that's
参数化的动态测试是
something completely new only really
真正全新的东西
possible with lambda expressions and
可能使用lambda表达式和
method references and in Java and above
方法参考以及Java和更高版本
so basically what we have is a different
所以基本上我们有一个不同
annotation that says the method is not a
说明该方法不是
test itself or rather a tense factory so
测试自己或者说是一个紧张的工厂
it generates tests and it generates
它生成测试并生成
tests in the form of this dynamic test
以这种动态测试的形式进行测试
interface here so instances of that this
接口在这里，这样的实例
dynamic test is imported here with the
动态测试与
static import that will create one for
静态导入将为
you based on don't give it a name this
您基于的名字不给这个
here be test in and it would be the
在这里进行测试，这将是
actual test is the body here this is
实际测试是这里的身体
this lambda expression or a method
此lambda表达式或方法
reference down here at the bottom so in
在底部参考这里
this example just to show how it works
这个例子只是为了展示它是如何工作的
basically however you want to create
基本上，但是你想创建
some kind of stream here we're iterating
我们正在迭代某种流
I'm getting the first ten even integers
我正在获取前十个偶数整数
and then we're mapping you through those
然后我们通过这些来映射您
on to one of these dynamic tests and
进行这些动态测试之一，
that returns as a stream of dynamic test
作为动态测试流返回
and then each one of these will get
然后每一个都会得到
invoked separately and report it as if
分别调用并报告，就好像
they were um standalone tests and we'll
他们是独立测试，我们将
see that in the IDE
在IDE中看到
speaking of which here we have repeated
说到这里，我们已经重复了
tests as I mentioned before you can just
就像我之前提到的那样测试
run that five times and what we see is
运行了五次，我们看到的是
that we have another level here so
我们在这里有另一个层次
repeated test is now a container and the
重复测试现在是一个容器，
things below that are the actual
以下是实际情况
indications for each of the repetitions
每个重复的指示
and with this other one here we can see
在这里，我们可以看到另一个
that you can have a custom display name
您可以有一个自定义的显示名称
so here we see this German meter how
所以我们在这里看到这台德国电表
long is one phone so it's like
一部手机很长，所以就像
repetition one two five
重复一二五
just translated into German for
刚刚翻译成德语
parametrized tests we have these
参数化测试，我们有这些
palindromes as I mentioned before this
我之前提到的回文
is the the source this is the stream of
是源，这是流
mom dead radar etc and if we run this
妈妈死了雷达等，如果我们运行这个
what we see is
我们看到的是
all right so we see each in each
好吧，所以我们看到每个
invocation they're coming up underneath
调用它们出现在下面
and we have the index display by default
并且默认情况下我们有索引显示
but you could override that if you
但如果您可以覆盖它
didn't want the indices displayed and
不想显示索引，并且
each one of these you can actually
您实际上可以
should be able to rerun an individual
应该能够重新运行个人
one which is a nice feature hopefully
希望这是一个不错的功能
that works because there's a filtering
之所以有效，是因为有一个过滤器
mechanism so we see it actually only ran
机制，所以我们看到它实际上只运行了
the one that I asked it's wrong and that
我问错了的那个
stream there in dynamic tests similar we
在类似我们的动态测试中流到那里
have the the first ten integers and some
有前十个整数和一些
strings here if we run that we see some
字符串在这里，如果我们运行，我们看到一些
similar results so dynamic test is a
类似的结果，所以动态测试是
class strings is the basically the
类字符串基本上是
factory and then the actual indications
出厂后再实际指示
of the bammy tests are listed as normal
正常测试中列出的正常
tests in the report and if you were to
在报告中进行测试，以及是否要
double click on one of those it would
双击其中一个
actually go to the factory right because
实际上去工厂是因为
there's no actual method there but in
那里没有实际的方法，但是
theory you should also be able to rerun
理论上你也应该能够重新运行
test B and we'll see if that works as
测试B，我们看看它是否可以像
well yes so that's working as well so
是的，这样也很好
the filtering you have this support all
您拥有的过滤功能全部支持
built into the hopefully all the IDS so
内置到所有IDS中
a parallel test execution in the past
过去的并行测试执行
you probably have done that with your
你可能已经用你的
build tool or some other third-party
构建工具或其他一些第三方
library we have built in support since
从那以后我们内置支持的库
5.3 and j-unit Jupiter for that so
5.3和j单位木星
basically you have to set it up you set
基本上你必须设置它
the Jane at Jupiter execution parallel
木星执行平行的简
enabled flag to true if you want to turn
如果您想将启用的标志设置为true
it on it's not on by default because you
默认情况下它不处于启用状态，因为您
may not want that it might make your
可能不希望它会使您
test would not work so well right if
测试不能很好地进行，如果
you're not ready for it to run in
您还没有准备好运行它
parallel you can also specify this in
您也可以在
the Jade platform properties file we
我们的Jade平台属性文件
review the launcher API or your IDE or
查看启动器API或您的IDE或
some of the build tools where's the
一些构建工具在哪里
system property so another thing you can
系统属性，因此您可以做的另一件事
do is you can configure the strategy to
您可以将策略配置为
be used for how how they should be
用于如何使用它们
actually in the parallel by default will
实际上默认情况下并行
just be dynamic based on the number of
只是根据数量来动态
CPUs and cores you have if you set a
如果您设置了CPU和核心
fixed number or a custom strategy if you
固定号码或自定义策略（如果您
wanted to another thing to keep in mind
想记住另一件事
though is um synchronization so you
虽然是同步，所以你
might want to pick or change the
可能想选择或更改
execution mode you can disable parallax
执行模式可以禁用视差
cue ssin on a per test
每次测试提示ssin
basis per class or or a method using the
每个类别的基础或使用
add execution annotation for example
例如添加执行注释
setting it to same thread and I would
将其设置为同一线程，我会
say don't run it concurrently but you
说不要同时运行，但是你
could also turn on concurrency for a
也可以为
particular one explicitly
明确地特定
and controlling the synchronization so
并控制同步，以便
sometimes things shouldn't run at the
有时候事情不应该在
same time all right you might think
同时你可能会想
about like the databases and kind of
关于数据库和类似的
locks so we have support for what are
锁，所以我们对
called resource locks and it just takes
称为资源锁，它只需要
a string basically the name of the thing
字符串，基本上是事物的名称
that's your resource this could be my
那是你的资源，这可能是我的
resource there's some default things
资源中有一些默认的东西
built in like system out system error
内置类似系统输出的系统错误
locale and stuff like that so you can
语言环境之类的东西，所以您可以
you can switch that up and you can also
您可以将其切换，也可以
change it from read write mode to to
将其从读写模式更改为
read mode so this all doctrine and then
阅读模式，所以这一切学说，然后
the reference journal but you can have
参考期刊，但您可以
good idea here what's what's supported
好主意，这里支持什么
so let's just take a quick look at what
所以让我们快速看一下
that might look like we have the
看起来像我们有
parameterize tests so right now if I run
参数化测试，所以现在如果我运行
it's calculating Fibonacci numbers I
它正在计算斐波那契数
have some log output and I'll see how
有一些日志输出，我会看看
long it takes approximately it's running
大概需要多长时间
a bit long it's still running would
有点长，它仍然在运行
appear so so they all finished
出现，所以他们都完成了
11 11 tests executed down to Fibonacci
11 11测试一直执行到斐波那契
of 44 and if we look in the console we
44，如果我们在控制台中查看
see it started out at about 8 they went
看到它从大约8点开始
down to 18 so I was about 10 seconds
降到18，所以我大约是10秒
right approximately now if we wanted to
如果我们想的话，大约现在
turn on the support for everything's
开启对所有事物的支持
running parallel we could just set this
并行运行，我们可以设置这个
flag I've done this in the junior
标记我已经在初中做到了
platform properties file enabled true
平台属性文件已启用true
and if I rerun it what's going to happen
如果我重新运行它，将会发生什么
now what do we see
现在我们看到了什么
you see ran all 11 and now if we look at
您会看到全部运行11，现在，如果我们看一下
the time just approximately it started
大概开始的时间
at 43 and went to 47 so that was more
在43岁时升至47岁，
like 4 seconds so quite a bit faster
大约4秒，所以快很多
another thing we see here on this
我们在这里看到的另一件事
logging output is I've shown the threads
日志输出是我已经显示了线程
if they're running on so you see that
如果他们在继续前进，那么你会看到
the fork/join pool is being used to run
fork / join池用于运行
these things in parallel we see multiple
这些东西并行，我们看到多个
different workers executing at the same
不同的工人在同一时间执行
time so that's one way to speed up your
时间，这是加快您的速度的一种方法
tests and your build and also within it
测试和您的构建以及其中的构建
with an IDE and that's pretty pretty
使用IDE，这非常漂亮
straightforward since 5.3 so another
从5.3开始很简单
thing about James Jupiters would really
关于詹姆斯·朱庇特的事情真的会
really focus on extensibility it's one
真正专注于可扩展性
thing that's been most important to me
对我来说最重要的事情
coming from spring where we have well
春天来了
supported for on extensions for Springs
在Springs扩展上受支持
integration session support and now we
集成会话支持，现在我们
have a similar somewhat comfortable
类似的有点舒服
model in and Jana Jupiter so we have a
模特和贾娜·朱庇特（Jana Jupiter），所以我们有一个
new model completely new it's not like
新模型全新，不是
the rules
规则
known from jr. for instead we have what
从小就知道。因为我们有什么
we call this on extension API extension
我们称其为扩展API扩展
itself is an interface which is the
本身就是一个接口
marker interface doesn't actually do
标记界面实际上并没有
anything but all the extensions that we
除了我们所有的扩展
have reside in this org Jane Jupiter API
已驻留在该组织的Jane Jupiter API中
extension package and you can implement
扩展包，您可以实施
it as many as you like which is nice so
随便你多
you can pick and choose which extension
您可以选择一个扩展名
API is implement in one concrete
API统一实现
implementation and you register that
实施，您注册
with that extend with for registering
与扩展与注册
one or more extensions at the same time
同时一个或多个扩展
so you know Jane and for you might know
所以你知道简，因为你可能知道
you couldn't have multiple runners we
你不能有多个跑步者
support multiple extensions at the same
同时支持多个扩展
time since the start for Jane and
自从Jane和
Jupiter and you can register these
木星，你可以注册这些
things via an interface on the interface
通过接口上的东西
class or method level where it's a meta
它是元的类或方法级别
annotation and the last part on you want
注解和您想要的最后一部分
to do this programmatically so you can
以编程方式执行此操作，以便您可以
use that registers extension on a field
使用在字段上注册扩展名
and that's somewhat analogous to the at
这有点类似于
rule support net classroom support you
规则支持网教室支持您
had from Jane at four so in terms of
从简到四点
lifecycle callbacks first up we have
首先是生命周期回调
before I'll call back and we have then
在我回电之前，我们有
an after I'll call back so before all is
一会儿我会回电，所以在一切之前
like before class and after all is like
就像上课前一样
after class and Jane to four and then
下课后，简到四，然后
the next time what we have before each
下次我们每个人都拥有
callback and after each and then we have
回调，然后每次
something immediately before and
紧接在之前的事物和
immediately after the execution of your
您执行后立即
test methods and those are the report
测试方法，这些是报告
and after test execution callbacks
和测试执行后的回调
so one thing keep in mind is that these
所以要记住的是，这些
extensions they wrap user-supplied
他们包装用户提供的扩展
lifecycle methods and and test methods
生命周期方法和测试方法
so if we were to look there's a kind of
所以如果我们看一下
invisible here at the for all methods
所有方法都不可见
and these would be that after all
而这些毕竟是
methods and an insight here would be
方法和见解将是
there before each methods and that at
在每种方法之前，以及
every two methods and then side here
每两种方法，然后在这里
would be actual act test method or
将是实际的行为测试方法或
parametrize tests and stuff like that
参数测试和类似的东西
next up we have various other API so we
接下来，我们还有其他各种API，因此我们
support as well
也支持
execution condition we'll talk more then
执行条件，然后我们再谈
detail a bit testing sis factory more
详细说明测试工厂
recent you can actually create CD a test
最近您实际上可以创建CD进行测试
instance on your own instead of letting
自己实例而不是让
jiggin it i'm san shaded for you test
跳动它，我为你遮荫测试
senses post processor that's so you can
感觉是后处理器，因此您可以
set things in it fields stuff like that
在其中设置内容
parameters oliver allows you to resolve
参数Oliver可以解决
arguments for constructors and methods
构造函数和方法的参数
and these last three basically on sum up
这最后三个基本上总结
support for dependency injection and
支持依赖注入和
spring actually makes use of the the
春天实际上利用了
latter tooth bomb but not the personal
后一颗牙齿炸弹，但不是个人
and this one is a mouthful test template
这是一口测试模板
indication context provider most people
指示上下文提供者大多数人
wouldn't implement it but that's how we
不会实现它，但这就是我们的方式
can ferment the support for things like
可以发酵对诸如此类的支持
the repeated tests and the parametrized
重复的测试和参数化
tests those are more advanced there's
测试那些更高级的
also support for handling exceptions so
还支持处理异常，因此
if you want to write kind of your own
如果你想自己写
expected exception extension you could
您可以预期的异常扩展
do that say you'd expect a certain kind
那样说你会期望某种
of exception to be thrown test Watchers
测试观察者抛出异常
brand new so it's inspired by the one in
全新，因此灵感来自于
JT 4 basically allows you to see it
JT 4基本上可以让您看到它
while when tests have been disabled and
当测试被禁用时
skipped and stuff like that also new is
跳过，类似的东西也很新
on display and generator allows you to
在显示器和发电机上，您可以
programmatically decide what the display
以编程方式决定显示什么
names should be and the method order so
名称应为，方法顺序应为
let's look at those last two in a bit
让我们看一下最后两个
more detail and these are actually
更多细节，这些实际上是
different from all the other extensions
与所有其他扩展名不同
because these two last two are applied
因为应用了最后两个
during the discovery phase so before the
在发现阶段之前
tests are actually I cute executed so
测试实际上我很可爱，所以
when a unit is looking for the tests so
当一个单位正在寻找测试时，
the source one explaining generator
源一解释生成器
basically allows you to generate custom
基本上可以让您生成自定义
display name for classes and methods you
显示您的类和方法的名称
can configure one view that I'm
可以配置一个我正在的视图
explaining generation annotation you can
可以解释世代注释
implement your own if you want to where
如果想在哪里实现自己的
you can use one of the built-in ones
您可以使用内置的之一
right now we have a standard one that's
现在我们有一个标准的
just the default behavior and we have
只是默认行为，我们有
one that's called replace underscores
一种叫做替换下划线
and not so surprisingly it replaces
并不奇怪，它取代了
underscores with spaces so a lot of
下划线带有空格，所以很多
people like to write camelcase based
人们喜欢写基于骆驼的
test method names or with underscores in
测试方法名称或下划线
them and this will just automatically
他们，这将自动
replace them so you have these nice
替换它们，以便您拥有这些不错的
readable names in that and report so
可读的名称并报告
method order allows you to control the
方法顺序可让您控制
order in which the test methods are
测试方法的顺序
executed within an individual test class
在单个测试类中执行
somewhat controversial but that's not
有些争议，但这不是
debated here in any case sometimes there
无论如何这里有时辩论
are needs for unit tests you probably
您可能需要单元测试
should not be using this but if you have
不应该使用这个，但是如果你有
something in this like kind of
这样的东西
integration test or functional test
集成测试或功能测试
where the order matters with some kind
在某种程度上顺序很重要的地方
of stateful thing or a data base then it
有状态的东西或数据库，那么它
might make sense to run them in a
将它们运行在一个
particular order and the way you can do
特定的订单和您可以做的方式
that is use that test method order you
即使用该测试方法命令您
can implement your own use one of the
可以实现自己使用之一
built-in ones we have alphanumeric what
内置的我们有字母数字什么
sorts the methods by their names and
按名称对方法进行排序，然后
optionally by the parameters if they
可选地通过参数（如果有）
have the same name is the order
订单名称相同
annotation one which allows you to
注释一，使您能够
specify a cordon specify the number so
指定警戒线，指定号码，以便
like one two three four and say run them
像一二三四说并运行它们
exactly this order and then we have one
正是这个顺序，然后我们有一个
for pseudo-random ordering which you can
进行伪随机排序
also be nice if you want to ensure that
如果您要确保
have no dependencies between your test
您的测试之间没有依赖关系
methods which is only a good idea then
方法，那只是一个好主意
you could set up random for that so this
您可以为此随机设置
disabled annotation mention that earlier
禁用的注释前面提到过
what's the significance this is this
这是什么意思
idea of conditional test execution and
条件测试执行的想法和
basically this is one place where the
基本上这是一个地方
extension model meets the Bergeron model
扩展模型符合Bergeron模型
we have this execution condition API you
我们有这个执行条件API
can implement that at disabled
可以在禁用时实现
annotation we have that and it's
注释，我们有那个
actually an implemented with the
实际上是用
disabled condition so it's not hard
残疾状况，这并不难
coded or only special to Jada Jupiter
编码或仅对贾达木星特别
anyone can write one of these things and
任何人都可以写这些东西之一，
this is basically a game changer in fact
这实际上是一个改变游戏规则的人
because anyone can write it so again
因为任何人都可以再写一次
Jane it for the only way you could have
简为可能的唯一方式
something disabled or ignore it is by
某些东西被禁用或忽略
saying out ignore and you couldn't have
说出来忽略，你不可能
any kind of dynamic conditions well
任何形式的动态条件
another feature we have is you can turn
我们拥有的另一个功能是您可以打开
this off if you want to maybe see of
如果您想看到
things that were disabled maybe you
被禁用的东西也许你
should now run then you can spacely
现在应该运行，然后您可以在空间上
specify a pattern specifying which
指定一个模式，指定哪个
conditions not to run for this
条件不为此而运行
particular test plan building conditions
特定的测试计划构建条件
so we have the disabled one since five
所以我们有一个五岁以下的残障人士
that oh and five one we introduced a
哦，五个，我们介绍了一个
number of wars so adding abled and
战争次数，因此增加了能力和
disabled if those might be deprecated
如果可能不推荐使用，则禁用
students maybe you don't want to look at
学生们也许你不想看
that but basically was allowing you to
那基本上是让你
use JavaScript to decide if the test
使用JavaScript决定测试是否
should run or not it's more popular
应该运行还是更受欢迎
things you have the ability to say run
你有能力说的事情
this test on a given JDK like JDK 8 9 10
在给定的JDK（例如JDK 8 9 10）上进行此测试
or not giving operating system like Mac
还是不给Mac这样的操作系统
or Linux or if I give it system property
或Linux，或者如果我给它系统属性
or environment variable is set or not so
或是否设置了环境变量
that gives you a lot of power out of the
这会给您很大的动力
box you just throw in these annotations
您只需在这些注解中放入框
and then I say enable or disable your
然后我说启用或禁用您的
tests so if you're on jana for a lot of
进行测试，以便您是否经常使用jana
people have some question do i have to
人们有一些疑问我必须
migrate the jana 5 or
迁移jana 5或
jana Jupiter or do I want to the answer
贾纳·朱庇特（Jana Jupiter）还是我想答案
is yes and no basically you can run your
是的，没有，基本上您可以运行
Jana for tests on the Jana platform with
Jana用于在Jana平台上进行测试
the vintage test engine without changing
老式测试引擎，无需更改
them they'll just work so in that sense
他们他们会这样工作
no but you can also run the jan you
不，但是您也可以运行jan
protest alongside Juvia test again in
与Juvia一起再次抗议
the same test report which is also quite
相同的测试报告也相当
nice so it's one of the benefits of this
很好，这是它的好处之一
platform idea and the same project same
平台构想与同一项目相同
idea same build you can also gradually
想法相同的建立，你也可以逐渐
migrate if you want to is this in Jan
如果您想在1月进行迁移
you for tests to join it for June
您需要参加6月的测试
Jupiter but you don't have to right you
木星，但你不必纠正你
can just keep your old tests as they are
可以保持您的旧测试不变
and then write new tests with James
然后和詹姆斯一起写新的测试
and that's what a lot of projects do but
这就是很多项目所做的，但是
if you do want to migrate some ideas or
如果您确实想移植一些想法或
some things keep in mind annotations so
有些事情请记住注释，因此
test is still called test but it's in
测试仍然称为测试，但是它在
the new package I'm at ignore is now at
我现在忽略的新包装现在在
disabled or one of those other disabled
残疾人或其他残疾人之一
variants before class and half the
上课前的变体和一半
classroom now before Island after all
毕竟现在在岛上的教室
same or before and after there's a
相同或之前和之后
before each and after each assertions
在每个断言之前和之后
have moved to a new class in a new
在新的班级里上了新班
package the same holds for assumptions
包装相同的假设
from Jane it for anything keep in mind
从Jane那里记住的任何事情
here is that this failure message comes
这是此失败消息
last when you're migrating so if you had
最后一次在您迁移时，如果您有
a string string string then you might
一个字符串，然后你可能会
have to make sure you get that right
必须确保你做对了
that's the arguments so we do have some
这就是论点，所以我们确实有一些
support for migrating Jana for rules
支持迁移Jana以获得规则
there's an ad naval rural migration
有一个海军的农村移民
support this is in a particular project
支持这是在特定项目中
that you have to include J and Jupiter
你必须包括J和木星
Gatien support its optional experimental
Gatien支持其可选的实验
it's probably not going to change but
它可能不会改变，但是
it's more of an optional feature but if
它更多是可选功能，但如果
you have that in then you put this on
你有那个然后你把它放在
your class then it's going to
你的课然后
automatically register three extensions
自动注册三个扩展
from Jupiter being these three so you
来自木星的这三个，所以你
get the support for things like Jana
得到诸如Jana之类的支持
force temporary folder error collector
强制临时文件夹错误收集器
an expected exception if you want to do
如果您想做的话，一个预期的例外
that another thing we added more
那件事我们增加了更多
recently is support for the JUnit 4 at
最近在以下位置支持JUnit 4
ignore annotation so if you want to
忽略注释，所以如果您想
continue to use that you can use this
继续使用，您可以使用此
different annotation that enabled unit
启用了单位的不同注释
for Migration support it will ignore
对于迁移支持，它将忽略
sorry register a condition for you that
很抱歉为您注册一个条件
supports this adding an orientation of
支持此添加方向
Jane 4 just like that disable one from
简4就这样禁用了一个
containing Jupiter I mean it also
包含木星，我的意思是
includes the support that we saw on the
包括我们在
previous slide and another thing is if
上一张幻灯片，另一件事是，如果
you're using Jane it orga Janet assume
您使用的是Jane it orga Janet，
these assumptions from Jane at 4 and in
这些假设来自Jane在4岁及以下
the process of migrating these will all
这些迁移的过程将全部
work out of the box since Jane and
自从Jane和
Jupiter 5.4 so that means anything that
木星5.4所以这意味着任何
throws a Jane at for assumption violated
将简扔向违反
exception will be counted as an aborted
异常将被视为已中止
test on Jane and Jupiter 5.4 in a bug
在Jane和Jupiter 5.4中测试一个bug
whereas previously it would have
而以前它会
actually failed the test and that was a
实际上没有通过测试，那是一个
bit confusing to some people so what's
有些人感到困惑，那是什么
new since the main major release for
自从主要主要版本发布以来新增
Jane had 5 some of the features as I
简与我一样有5项功能
mentioned when I didn't mention was we
我没有提到的时候提到的是我们
introduced to Janet maven bomb so if
介绍给珍妮特·梅文炸弹，如果
you're not using spring boot you might
你不使用弹簧靴，你可能
want to look into the bomb for
想调查炸弹
simplifying dependency management
简化依赖关系管理
Prelude at execution we saw that there's
在执行前奏时，我们看到有
also support for capturing system
还支持捕获系统
system error they came along with the
他们伴随的系统错误
parallel test execution we mentioned
我们提到的并行测试执行
that custom test sources for dynamic
自定义测试源的动态
tests if you're into dynamic tests if
测试您是否要进行动态测试
you're in a cotton the cotton support
你在棉花里
improves over time from external
随着时间的推移从外部改善
contributors that are that are really
真正的贡献者
keen on using cotton register extension
热衷于使用棉花登记册扩展名
intestines Factory and several more more
肠工厂等等
recently some things to highlight
最近有些事情要强调
there's now a new Jane at Jupiter
木星现在有一个新的简
dependency that you can use so basically
基本上可以使用的依赖
arguably a grades all the main things
可以说是对所有主要事物进行了评分
from Jane and Jupiter and you can just
来自简和木星，你可以
say you depend on Jane and Jupiter
说你依靠简和木星
instead of the individual artifacts so
而不是单个文物
it just makes things easier the xml
它只会使xml变得更容易
report generating lists there they made
报告他们在那里制作的清单
that public recently there's a new test
那个公众最近有一个新的测试
kit so if you're writing your own test
工具包，如果您正在编写自己的测试
engine if you want to go that route or
引擎，如果你想走那条路或者
if you want to test an extension you've
如果您想测试扩展程序
written for Jane in Jupiter then you can
在木星上为简写的话，你可以
use the new test kit in tradition and
传统上使用新的测试套件，
504 and that makes it much easier to to
504，这样更容易
test those things temperature support so
测试温度支持的那些东西
that was very popular requested their
那很受欢迎，要求他们
support for that in Jane at four with a
支持简在四点钟
rule and now we have support for that in
规则，现在我们对此表示支持
and Jane and Jupiter since 5.4 so you
从5.4开始，简和木星就如此
can basically temperature injected as a
基本上可以将温度注入
path where as a file and you can work
文件所在的路径，您可以在其中工作
with that in your constructor your test
在您的构造函数中进行测试
methods etc and then Jaden will clean it
方法等，然后贾登会清理它
up for you afterwards so basically just
之后为您服务，所以基本上
deleting the directory
删除目录
it's all these ordering for tests you
这些就是所有测试顺序
can also order the extensions if you're
也可以订购扩展
registering them without register
无需注册即可注册
extension via fields via the at order
通过at顺序通过字段扩展
annotation
注解
mm-hmm okay so what's up I'm coming in
嗯，好吧，我要怎么了
genuine 5.5 we already have some
真正的5.5我们已经有一些
milestones out we'll have support for
里程碑，我们将为
boolean values and value source these
布尔值和这些值的来源
built-in conditions like running a
内置条件，例如运行
particular OS so I'm secure I'm JD cases
特定的操作系统，所以我很安全，属于JD案件
like that you've gotta use repeatable
就像你必须使用可重复的
annotation so that so how them declared
注释，以便它们如何声明
multiple times in terms of timeouts I
关于超时我多次
showed you how to do that
告诉你怎么做
programmatically without a cert timeout
以编程方式没有证书超时
and we're going to introduce support for
我们将介绍对
declaring that you want a particular
声明您想要一个特定的
timeout for all of your test methods in
您所有测试方法的超时时间
particular class and stuff like that
特殊的班级之类的东西
there's also a new invocation
还有一个新的调用
interceptor a extension API that allows
拦截器扩展API，允许
you to do things like instituting the
您要做诸如建立
code and a user divine thread which
代码和用户神圣的线程
might work nicely if using something
如果使用某些东西可能会很好地工作
like SWT and if you're doing something
例如SWT，如果您正在做某事
more low-level like writing your own
更底层的喜欢自己写
test engine there's a new config we'll
测试引擎，我们将有一个新的配置
just test discovery basis implementation
只是测试发现基础的实现
you can build off and extend from if you
你可以建立和扩展，如果你
want so in the backlog there's some
想要在积压中有一些
things we're looking at in the future we
未来我们正在寻找的东西
want to add support at some point for
想在某个时候增加支持
using a custom class loader for support
使用自定义类加载器获得支持
for a programmatic extension management
用于程序扩展管理
instead of just declaring it with
而不是仅仅用
annotations we want our support for
我们希望我们支持的注释
first-class support for test Suites
对测试套件的一流支持
parametrize test classes so I mentioned
参数测试类，所以我提到
we have parametrized test methods right
我们有参数化的测试方法
now but we're looking at adding support
现在，但我们正在考虑增加支持
for parent izing a test class and having
家长设定测试班并
the same test class run multiple times
同一测试类可以运行多次
with different input scenario tests is
使用不同的输入方案测试是
something else on we're looking at where
我们正在寻找其他东西
you have multiple steps and they go in a
你有多个步骤，他们进入一个
particular sequence and a new reporting
特定顺序和新报告
format so I've already shown some things
格式，所以我已经显示了一些东西
like the custom display names and that
像自定义显示名称之类的
dynamic tests and we have different
动态测试，我们有不同的
levels of hierarchies in the end the
最终的层次结构
tests and we need a new reporting format
测试，我们需要一种新的报告格式
that supports these kind of things so
支持这些事情，所以
we're hoping to get that out in the next
我们希望在下一个
couple months or so but it'll probably
几个月左右，但可能
take a while for the whole world to
花了一段时间让整个世界
catch up so we're probably using
赶上，所以我们可能正在使用
different formats for awhile or both at
一段时间内使用不同的格式，或同时使用
the same time so that's it for the core
同时是核心
about gene that we'll talk a bit about
关于基因，我们将稍作讨论
spring and gene Jupiter which makes
春天和木星的基因
sense when since Reds spring io
自从红军春季运动会开始
so who was actually used Jane it Jupiter
所以谁真正使用过简·木星
with spring anyone okay six seven people
到了春天，任何人都可以，六个七个人
I hope it went well if not come talk to
我希望它能顺利进行
me about it
关于我
alright so it's been fully integrated in
好吧，所以它已经完全集成在
Spring Framework since five deado of
Spring Framework自从五死
spring and it supports all of the core
春天，它支持所有核心
integration testing features that you've
您拥有的集成测试功能
come to know and I love with spring and
认识，我爱春天，
spring boot but in addition it does some
spring boot ，但除此之外
new things that weren't possible with
不可能的新事物
Jana Fortis and G so we have support for
Jana Fortis和G，所以我们对
constructor and Method injection
构造函数和方法注入
dependency injection using annotations
使用注解进行依赖注入
annotations from spring like at Auto
来自Spring的注释，例如在Auto处
wired qualifier and value and we also
有线的限定词和价值，我们也
have support for conditional test
支持条件测试
execution with spell expressions let's
用咒语表达来执行
talk about that in a minute yet we have
稍等一下，我们有
some special annotations we can use to
我们可以使用一些特殊的注释
simplify things it also works with
简化它也可以使用的东西
Spring Framework 4.3 if you happen to be
如果碰巧是Spring Framework 4.3
stuck on for three and can't upgrade to
卡住了三个，无法升级到
five five one or that upcoming five two
五五一或即将到来的五二
and that's in my I'm getting over
那是在我的身边
depository and there's instructions
存放处和指示
there for how you can use it so some
那里有如何使用它的方法
people do use that if they want to go
人们确实想去那里
ahead and use Jana Jupiter now with
继续使用，现在使用Jana Jupiter
spring framework for three but just keep
春天的框架，但三个保持
in mind that it doesn't get new features
请记住，它没有新功能
so the new features all go into 5.2 for
因此新功能全部加入5.2
example for upcoming spring 5.2 so to
即将到来的Spring 5.2的示例
set it up in Jana 4 we had our Spring
在Jana 4设置它，我们有了春天
runner and Jana Jupiter we have a spring
亚军和贾纳·朱庇特，我们有一个春天
extension you can say extend with spring
延伸可以说是用弹簧延伸
extension if you want to do it manually
扩展名，如果您想手动执行
but we have some nice composed
但我们有一些不错的组成
annotation so that's ring Jana config
批注，这样就可以实现Jana配置
which combines the at concentration
结合了浓度
notation plus the registration of spring
记号加上春天的注册
and similarly for web support it
以及类似的网络支持
combines the previously with added web
结合以前的网站
app configuration so it just simplifies
应用程序配置，因此可以简化
configuration it makes you type less and
配置它使您键入的内容更少，
these at enable different disable of
这些在启用不同的禁用
annotations they have the same names as
批注与它们具有相同的名称
the one from from Jupiter unfortunately
不幸的是来自木星的那个
but these two from the spring package
但是这两个来自春季包
work with spell expressions so you can
使用咒语表达，因此您可以
interact with beans from your
与您的咖啡豆互动
application context and do things like
应用程序上下文并执行类似的操作
that
那
so brand new since about a week some
所以大约一个星期以来是全新的
people have been asking for this you
人们一直在要求你
might know that was spring I
可能知道那是春天
historically had to write at Auto wired
历史上不得不写在自动有线
on a constructor to have it picked but
在构造函数上选择它，但是
since spring 4.3 you no longer have to
从4.3版本开始，您不再需要
write at Auto wired on a constructor if
如果在构造函数的自动连线上写
there's just a one spring we'll pick it
只有一个春天，我们来挑选
in and perform dependency injection for
并执行依赖注入
you so basically this what this does
你基本上就是这样
here is allows you have the same feature
这是允许您具有相同的功能
in Jana Jupiter went
在Jana Jupiter去了
with spring so by default as mentioned
带弹簧，因此默认情况下如前所述
you have to have it annotated but this
您必须对其进行注释，但这
default can be changed this is a globe
默认可以更改，这是一个地球仪
little fault now you can do this by
小毛病，现在你可以做到这一点
setting the spring test constructor Auto
设置弹簧测试构造函数自动
are a flag to true it is by default
是true的标志，默认情况下
false you can do that via JVM system
假，您可以通过JVM系统执行此操作
property or this bring properties
财产或这带来财产
mechanism which is a spring dot
弹簧点的机制
properties file in the root of the class
类根目录中的属性文件
bathroom or you can override on a
浴室，也可以在
particular class level mat test
特殊等级的垫子测试
constructor Auto wire is true or Auto
构造函数自动连线为true或Auto
Wireless false to change whatever the
无线假改变任何
default is for this particular class so
默认为此特定类，因此
spring boot since spring boot 2.1
从spring boot 2.1开始的spring boot
there's been pretty good support for it
有很好的支持
for jane and super i'm here have an
对于简和超级，我在这里
example some custom config so i wanted
例如一些自定义配置，所以我想要
to write a spring be test with add
用add编写spring be test
spring be tests aptly named i wanted to
春天被测试恰当地命名为我想
have the automatic
有自动
ma community support and I wanted to use
妈的社区支持，我想用
Jane and Jupiter so I use these three
简和木星，所以我用这三个
annotations here I'm saying that I want
这里的注释我是说我想要
to be able to declare it on my classes
可以在我的课上声明
and don't forget to save it at runtime
并且不要忘记在运行时保存它
otherwise it's not in the bytecode and
否则它不在字节码中，
the frameworks can't see it and
框架看不到
historically you would have had to say
从历史上讲，您不得不说
extend with spring extension but since
用弹簧延伸来延伸，但是由于
spring boo to that one spring boot test
spring boo到那个 spring boot 测试
and the other slice annotations you
和其他切片注释
might know some of the tests like the
可能知道某些测试，例如
JSON tests things like that they're all
JSON测试类似的东西
meta annotated with this at extend with
在此扩展的meta带有
spring extension so you can just delete
春天的延伸，所以你可以删除
that since spring be to it one in the
从春天开始就成为
course of the upcoming spring boot 2.2
即将到来的 spring boot 2.2的过程
so here I have screen be tests Auto
所以这里我有屏幕测试自动
configure and I've said transactional I
配置，我说过交易
have a sample application called spring
有一个名为spring的示例应用程序
events and this is just for testing the
事件，这只是为了测试
web tier in that so as an example I
网络层，例如
wanted to show that with this method
想用这种方法来证明
level dependency injection from spring
从Spring注入级别依赖
and it's mock and we see this getting
它是模拟的，我们看到了
auto configured for us from spring boot
从 spring boot 为我们自动配置
so I can just say at spring events web
所以我只能在春季活动网站上说
tests on various controller tests in my
在我的各种控制器测试上进行测试
project this is just for my project
专为我的项目而设计
optionally use a custom display name and
（可选）使用自定义显示名称和
here list events and I'm saying I'd auto
这里列出事件，我是说我会自动
wired
有线
mocking me see so that gets injected I
嘲笑我，让我被注入
can just use it locally and this notion
可以在本地使用它，这个概念
here of using Auto wired on a particular
这里使用在特定的
method it could be a good practice but
方法，这可能是一个好习惯，但是
it could also be a worst practice if
如果这也是最糟糕的做法
you're doing it all over the place then
你要在整个地方做
don't do it on the constructor if you
如果您不对构造函数执行此操作
want or do it on it before each method
在每种方法之前都想要或要做
so you just set it up once so you have
所以你只需要设置一次就可以了
to basically get a feel for that but
基本上可以体会到这一点，但是
it's an option to do it at the test
在测试中可以选择
level as well
水平也
so one thing that I'm people have run
所以我是人的一件事
into rather frequently in recent months
最近几个月相当频繁
people who were on various version of
使用各种版本的人
spring boots who wanted to upgrade to
想要升级到的 spring boot
the latest and greatest version of Jane
简的最新最好的版本
of five there was a later version than
五分之一的版本比
the one that spring movements with him
和他一起运动的那个人
and they couldn't figure out how to do
他们不知道该怎么办
it so it's been a very popular question
所以这是一个非常受欢迎的问题
in various forums for example in this
例如在各种论坛中
stack overflow question that I answered
我回答的堆栈溢出问题
and the answer is pretty simple read the
答案很简单，请阅读
documentation for spring boot it tells
它告诉了Spring Boot文档
you how to upgrade dependencies but to
您如何升级依赖关系，但要
spell it out for you you have to find
为你拼出来，你必须找到
out what the name of the the version is
指出版本的名称是什么
that spring boot considers as a name and
spring boot 认为是一个名字，
for Jane of five it's Jane at Jupiter
五分之一的简是木星上的简
version for Gradle you would set it like
您将设置为Gradle的版本
this and for maven you would set it like
这和行家，你会喜欢
that so in your main palm and you can
这样，在您的主掌上，您就可以
make sure using the the latest and
确保使用最新的
greatest
最伟大的
now the upcoming or the recently at
现在即将到来或最近
least two days ago spring boot to the
至少两天前的 spring boot
two mile so three already has the
两英里，所以三个已经
version sets of that because that's the
版本集，因为那是
latest version of Jane and Jupiter but
简和木星的最新版本，但
it could be that Jane that Jupiter 5.5
木星5.5可能就是简
comes out after the supreme boot final
在最高引导决赛之后出现
GA release so you might want to still
GA发布，因此您可能仍然希望
know how to upgrade then or any point in
知道如何然后升级或在任何点
the future so as an example we'll see if
以未来为例，我们将看看
this works I went to what would Joshua
这个作品我去了约书亚
Wong say start the spring diorite and
黄说开始春天的闪闪发亮，
picked tu-22m3 and then um went with
选择了tu-22m3，然后um与
great ones like the defaults and what
伟大的像默认值和什么
happened was I downloaded and unzipped
发生的是我下载并解压缩了
it imported it into my IDE and that's
它将其导入到我的IDE中，这就是
this sorry demo and if we look at the
这个抱歉的演示，如果我们看看
versions what we see in there we do see
我们在那里看到的版本
screen boot 2.0 so like that m3 and if
屏幕启动2.0，如M3，如果
we look at the the Jane two versions
我们来看简两个版本
it's got Jane 25.4 tattoo in there and
那里有简25.4纹身，
the spring stuff it has the ladies and
春天的东西，它有女士们和
greatest spring test 5 - om - so all the
最佳弹簧测试5-om-所有
new features I talked about there you
我在那儿谈论的新功能
can you can use those so what does it do
你能用那些吗，它能做什么
it creates a basically application she's
它创建了一个基本的应用程序
ever used to start the screen do you
曾经用来启动屏幕吗
know it creates it with Jane at four by
知道它是在四点钟与简一起创造的
default using spring runner spring boot
默认使用SpringRunner弹簧靴
test and what was this little trick I
测试，这是什么小技巧
showed you I said aha spring boots
告诉你我说过啊哈春靴
already annotated with extend with
已经用扩展注释
spring extensions so you can use Jane
春天扩展，因此您可以使用简
and Jupiter agenda at for whichever you
和木星的议程在任何你
pick and the annotation here that's the
选择，这里的注释是
mortgage Odin
奥丁抵押
tests that's Janet four and then this
测试是珍妮特四，然后这个
will of course run shouldn't be a
当然会运行不应该
surprise ran pretty fast but what if we
惊喜跑得很快，但是如果我们
wanted to get rid of the Jana for stuff
想摆脱贾纳的东西
right then for starters we'd have to
然后，对于初学者，我们必须
make sure we get the right annotation
确保我们得到正确的注释
from Janet Jupiter and this thing is
来自珍妮特·朱庇特（Janet Jupiter），这件事是
already registering the extension force
已经注册了延伸力
so it should hopefully just run now it's
所以它应该应该现在就运行
running with Jana five that worked fine
与Jana 5一起运行正常
and just to prove it to you alright you
只是为了向你证明
can take off the the public if you want
如果愿意，可以让公众脱颖而出
to and then it'll still run and just as
到然后它仍然会运行，就像
an example some people like to have
一些人喜欢的例子
things private final and immutable if
事物是私有的，如果不可变
you wanted to I don't have any beans in
你想我没有豆
my application context environnement a
我的应用程序环境a
speller right from spring environment
春季环境中的拼写者
why does it peeps make that a capital e
为什么偷看使资本成为资本
no one knows so now I have this private
没人知道，所以我现在有这个私人的
final mutable field that I want to be
我想成为的最终可变字段
injected yeah and I can make a
是的，我可以做一个
constructor that's supported you start
您开始支持的构造函数
your four fields should all work all
您的四个领域都应该全部起作用
right that's there what happens if I run
对，如果我跑步，那会发生什么
the test now any guesses no parameters
现在测试中没有任何猜测
Oliver I couldn't find it so what did I
奥利弗我找不到它，所以我做了什么
say before the default I said if you say
在默认值之前说
ID on a wired from spring and that
从春天开始的电线上的ID
should work right that was a one option
应该正确地工作，这是一个选择
and then I said well what if you didn't
然后我很好地说，如果你不这样做
want to do that said if you wanted to
想这样做，如果你想
override locally test constructor
覆盖本地测试构造函数
that should also work we run the test
那也应该工作，我们进行测试
again that works but what if you wanted
再次有效，但是如果您想
to change it globally for our psyche
为了我们的心理在全球范围内改变它
that kind of superclass or on interfaces
这种超类或接口
of like that what if we wanted to do it
就像那样，如果我们想这样做
globally for the whole for the whole
在全球范围内
project so enough around again it's
再次围绕着足够的项目
gonna fail one option would be to take
失败的一种选择就是采取
that I hope I already have a right
我希望我已经有权利
configuration set up here I'll do if we
在这里设置配置，如果我们
don't call it X if we say spring test
如果说春季测试，不要称它为X
constructor Hardware equals true I'm
构造函数硬件等于true我是
setting this year for the VM for this
为此设置今年的虚拟机
current test but you could set it for
当前测试，但您可以将其设置为
your whole build wherever your one of
您的整个构建，无论您的其中一个
the properties files if I run it now
属性文件（如果现在运行）
will also see that it runs so this is
还将看到它运行，所以这是
this kind of idea where you can have the
这种想法，你可以有
private final and mutable fields in your
您的私人最终和可变字段
tests and use basic dependency injection
测试并使用基本的依赖注入
just like you would and your normal
就像你和你的正常人一样
components in spring like in that
像这样的弹簧组件
service at controller etc so I'm glad
在控制器等服务，所以我很高兴
the demo worked you never know with
该演示有效，您从未了解过
these kind of things all right it's
这些事情好吗
getting involved if you want to help out
参与进来，如果你想帮忙
you can participate on on github for
您可以在github上参与
chain 5 reporting issues suggesting new
链5报告问题提示新问题
features participating in discussions of
参与讨论的功能
course you can also answer questions on
当然您也可以回答有关的问题
Stack Overflow or there's a Gitter
堆栈溢出或混乱
channel you can participate in as well
您也可以参加的频道
and if you want to you can support the
如果您愿意，可以支持
Jaina team with donations via study HQ
吉安娜团队通过研究总部捐款
that helps with the further development
有助于进一步发展
before they do contribute use in their
在他们为自己做贡献之前
spare time
空余时间
so in closing yep I have some resources
所以在结束时我有一些资源
here for for accessing gene it basically
这里基本上是为了访问基因
started Jenny org get a JUnit 5 there's
开始Jenny org获得一个JUnit 5
a bunch of links there you can see
一堆链接，您可以看到
there's a link to the reference guide
有指向参考指南的链接
Java doc and get help so like that
Java文档并获得帮助，就像这样
also I'm get her and stack overflow
我也得到她，堆栈溢出
their links to those and then the user
他们与那些链接，然后是用户
guide as well Dimon's uses presentation
指南以及戴蒙的使用演示
or my account s brandon on github jane
或我在github jane上的帐户的brandon
to five demo I also used some examples
到五个演示，我还使用了一些示例
straight from the the user guide in Jane
直接来自Jane中的用户指南
in five so one thing we do there is the
五分之一，我们要做的是
the example is in user guide actually
该示例实际上在用户指南中
executed in the build so you're
在构建中执行，因此您
guaranteed to that they work the
保证他们工作
examples there and you can copy them
那里的例子，你可以复制它们
from the documentation project if you
从文档项目中，如果您
want so you have a few minutes if there
想要，所以你有几分钟的时间
are questions I can answer them if not I
是我可以回答的问题
have more demos I could go through but
我有更多的演示可以通过
I'll open up two if two questions first
如果先问两个问题，我将打开两个
no question
没有问题
yeah and you know the way you said you
是的，你知道你说的方式
don't have to declare public on the test
不必在测试中宣布公开
anymore yeah so does that give you any
是的，那也能给你带来什么
advantages means you can type less yeah
优势意味着您可以少打字
that's it and yeah and the other thing
就是这样，是的，另一件事
is some people don't like to see the
是有些人不喜欢看到
test is as public types when they search
当他们搜索时，测试就是公共类型
for types and different packages stuff
用于类型和不同包装的东西
like that so that could be an advantage
这样可能是一个优势
but it's mainly about less is more we
但是主要是因为少即是多
don't make you type it anymore if you're
如果您正在，请不要再键入它
using your IDE and it's tutoring before
使用您的IDE，并且在之前进行辅导
we make some public I wouldn't
我们公开一些我不会的
personally worry about it if I type in a
如果我输入一个，我个人会担心
new one I just don't type the word
新的，我只是不输入单词
public but that's it anywhere else
公开，但仅此而已
yes version 4 to 5 how affects their
是的版本4至5如何影响他们的
performance let's say our application
性能说我们的应用
takes 15 minutes in our tests like let's
在我们的测试中需要15分钟，就像我们
like between like 15 minutes and half
大约15分钟到一半之间
hour so if you migrate to the 5 version
小时，所以如果您迁移到5版本
what you're thinking about does it
你在想什么
affect the performance like we thought
像我们认为的那样影响性能
if you thought about the performance if
如果您考虑过性能
you're I'm just thinking about this
你就是我在想这个
parallel execution so its type well that
并行执行，因此其类型很好
would make it faster if your code works
如果您的代码有效，它将使速度更快
well for for running in parallel for
非常适合并行运行
sure but in general so there were a few
当然可以，但是总的来说有一些
bugs along the way where we had some
我们有一些错误的方式
things we had to optimize but as far as
我们必须优化的东西
you know currently there shouldn't be
你知道目前不应该
really any performance difference yeah
真的有任何性能差异吗
should should join above about the same
应该加入以上大致相同
but with the parallel stuff you can make
但有了平行的东西，你可以做
it faster and that's nice so in the past
它更快，这很好，所以过去
you could have done that with the build
您可以通过构建完成
may even like working in the I know it's
甚至可能喜欢在我工作的地方
a barrel or Gradle
桶或摇篮
but Gradle does it differently and with
但是Gradle的做法与众不同
this this does it within a class like
这是在像
the methods within a class or anyone's
类或任何人的方法
game over is what the sign says so
比赛结束就是标志说的
thanks for coming if you have any
感谢您的光临
questions you can catch me outside
你可以在外面捉住我的问题
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]